jokezone.in 2012-12-27

# Privacy

This privacy statement is intended to give you, the user of this website, an awareness about what information this website collects, how this information is used, and how this affects your privacy while using this site.

### Logging and Statistics

When a user views a page, image or other item on this site, the user’s IP address, browser type, and the site you came from is stored in a log file. None of this information can be used to personally identify an individual user. The details stored in this log file may be used to provide statistics about the usage of this site, for the purpose of improving the site and to provide statistical information to advertisers. Only aggregated information is given, and the log file itself is not available to the public.

### Cookies and Advertising

A cookie is a piece of information stored on the user’s browser by a website, which can be read later. A cookie may be used to remember something about a user.

Users may choose not to accept cookies through privacy settings in most web browsers. The relevant setting can usually be found in a ‘Privacy’ section under the browser’s options dialog. Refer to your web browser’s documentation for more information.

It is possible to use this site even if your browser is configured to reject cookies.

We do not store or retrieve any personally identifiable information about users through our use of cookies.

Advertisers on this site store and read cookies on the user’s browser, and collect other statistical information through the use of web beacons, in the course of displaying relevant advertisements on the site. We do not have any access to the information from these cookies and they are not used to store or retrieve any personally identifiable information about users.

Our main third party advertiser is Google Adsense

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/).

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### Newsletter

If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. The email addresses will not be sold, hired or given out to any third parties. The email addresses are used only by Jokes Place’s email provider to provide ‘The JokeZone Newsletter’ to recipients who have requested it.

We care deeply about the privacy of our subscribers, and we make every effort to ensure the confidentiality of our list is maintained.

### Tell-A-Friend

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s email address. This feature may also ask for the sender’s email address. This site will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Some of the information used in this feature will be logged for security purposes. The personal message (if any) accompanying the email will not be logged or stored in any way. The email addresses will be retained for security purposes and will not be placed into a mailing list, or used for any further mailings. They will not be sold, hired or given out to any third parties.

### Special Offers

We send all new newsletter subscribers a welcoming email. Subscribers will receive the Jokes Place Newsletter on a regular basis, and will not receive other mailings. The Jokes Place Newsletter is advertiser supported and may contain some advertisements. Please see our choice and opt-out below.

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify members by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
